Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Publications Collection, 1887-2005 RL.00741
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Oversize Materials, 7 boxes
  - International--London Office, 1967-2001 and undated
    - 1967 (Box OV3)
      - 40 Berkeley Square (Box OV3)
    - 1990
      - JWT Rises to the Challenge of Europe (Box OV3)
    - 2001
      - Knightsbridge Green Blueprint (Box OV3)
    - Undated
      - JWT London (Box OV3)
  - International--Other Offices Publications, 1972-2003 and undated
    - Asia-Pacific
      - Don't Blink: The Third Beat Passion, 2002 (Box OV4)
    - Australia
      - J. Walter Thompson Co. Limited, 1983 (Box OV4)
    - Belgium
      - J. Walter Thompson, 1984 (Box OV4)
    - Brazil
      - Jota Dabliu Te, undated (Box OV4)
    - Denmark
      - Naget om JWT før og nu, 1972 (Box OV4)
    - Europe/Middle East/Africa
      - Benchmark, 2001 (Box OV4)
      - Passion '03: JWT Europe, Middle East, Africa, 2003 (Box OV4)
    - Germany
      - Portrait, 1984 (Box OV4)
    - Italy
      - Who's Who, undated (Box OV5)
    - Mexico
      - Passion '03: JWT Latinoamerica, 2003 (Box OV5)
    - Philippines
      - J. Walter Thompson, 1982 (Box OV5)
    - Spain
      - Esto No Es Un Cuchillo de Palo, 1991 (Box OV5)
    - Sweden
      - Resultattavlor, 1984 (Box OV5)
  - Subsidiaries and Related Firms, 1975-1985
    - EA International/Euro Advertising (Paris, France)
      - EA Euro-Lyon, 1979 (Box OV6)
      - Press Information, 1980 (Box OV6)
    - Landsdowne Advertising (New York, N.Y.)
      - Landsdowne, 1979 (Box OV6)
      - Landsdowne Marketing Limited, 1975 (Box OV6)
    - Lord, Geller, Federico, Einstein
      - LGFE, 1981, 1984-1985, 3 folders (Box OV7)